This exercise has given us an array
and we're asked to return
the string example from this array.
So taking a closer look, you can see
that this array has two elements.
Each of those elements is also an array.
The first element is an array
that contains three strings.
And the second element is an array
that contains two elements,
which are also strings.
And you can see that the string example is
the first element in the second sub array.
We can access this second
element in our two element array
with the array last method.
So I'm going to use P to output that
and let's run our code and see that.
So now we see the last element of our
array, ah, which is a two element array
example, is the first
element of this array.
Knowing that we want to return the string
example, we can simply chain a method
called to the array first method.
This will return the first element
of the last element of the array,
let's output this.
And we see the stirring example,
you can read about these array methods
and more in the ruby documentation
for the array class.